Guide to the University of Chicago Office of the President, Kimpton Administration Records 1892-1960
University of Chicago Library
- Series I: General Files
  - American Society of Planning Officials, 1957 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - American Society for Public Administration, 1953-1960 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - American Universities Field Staff, Inc., 1955-1960 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Analysis of Ideas and the Study of Methods, Committee on, 1955-1958 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Anastaplo, George, 1952-1959 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Anatomy, Department of, 1954-1959 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Andelson, Robert F., 1952-1956 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Animal quarters, 1954-1958 (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Announcements, 1951-1960 (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Annuity agreements, 1953-1960 (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - Anthropology, Department of, 1951-1960 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Anthropology, Department of, Robert Redfield, 1951-1959 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Anthropology, Department of, space, 1953-1958 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Anthropology, Department of, Tama Indian Program, Sol Tax, 1954-1957 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Anti-Vivisection, 1951-1959 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Applied Sciences, School of, proposed, 1956-1960 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Appointments, Reappointments, and Promotions to Tenure, Subcommittee on Standards, 1957-1959 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Archaeological Institute of America, 1955-1958 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Architects, 1957-1960 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Area, Committee on, 1949-1960 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Area Programs, University-Wide Committee on Long-Range Plans for, 1960 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Argentina, 1958 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Argonne Cancer Research Hospital, 1947-1960 (Box 25, Folder 4-5)
  - Argonne National Laboratory, 1946-1955 (Box 25, Folder 6-7)
  - Argonne National Laboratory, 1958-1960 (Box 26, Folder 1-2)
  - Argonne National Laboratory, experimental boiling water reactor, 1956-1960 (Box 26, Folder 3-4)
  - Argonne National Laboratory, general advisory committee, 1953-1955 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Argonne National Laboratory, history and background, 1949-1957 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Argonne National Laboratory, news clippings, 1960 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Arizona, University of, 1954-1960 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Arkansas, University of, 1957-1960 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Art, Department of, 1951-1960 (Box 27, Folder 4-5)
  - Art Institute of Chicago, 1949-1959 (Box 27, Folder 6-7)
  - Art Institute of Chicago, joint degree program in the center for art studies, 1959 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Asia, 1951-1957 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Aspen Institute for Humanistic Studies, 1949-1960 (Box 27, Folder 10-12)
  - Aspen Institute for Humanistic Studies, Branch College, 1952-1953 (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - Aspen Institute for Humanistic Studies, Branch College, Committee on, 1953 (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - Associated Clubs of Woodlawn, 1960 (Box 27, Folder 15)
  - Associated Colleges of Illinois, 1951-1956 (Box 27, Folder 16)
  - Associated Midwest Universities, 1957-1960 (Box 28, Folder 1-2)
  - Associated Midwest Universities, articles of incorporation and by-laws, University of Chicago membership, 1957-1959 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Associated Universities, Incorporated, 1953-1954 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Association of American Colleges, 1950-1960 (Box 28, Folder 5-7)
  - Association of American Law Schools, 1951-1958 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Association of American Medical Colleges, 1949-1960 (Box 28, Folder 9-12)
  - Association of American Universities, 1951-1960 (Box 29, Folder 1-4)
  - Association of American Universities, annual meeting, Chicago, Illinois, October 25-26, 1960 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Association of American Universities, Association of Graduate Schools, 1948-1960 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Association of American Universities, Association of Graduate Schools, 1949-1957 (Box 30, Folder 1-2)
  - Association of American Universities, Association of Graduate Schools, annual meeting, 1952-1956 (Box 30, Folder 3-5)
  - Association of American Universities, Association of Graduate Schools, Newsletter and Clearing House, 1950-1956 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Association of American Universities, Association of Graduate Schools, "The Dwarfs," special group of deans from privately supported universities, 1955-1958 (Box 30, Folder 7-8)
  - Association of American Universities, Association of Graduate Schools, "The Dwarfs," special group of deans from privately supported universities, 1959-1960 (Box 31, Folder 1-3)
  - Association of American Universities, Committee on Foundation Grants, 1956-1958 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Association of American Universities, Committee on Indirect Costs of Research Grants, 1958-1960 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Association of American Universities, Committee on Security Problems, 1954-1955 (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Association of American Universities, membership, 1954-1960 (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Association of American Universities, minutes of meetings, 1950-1959 (Box 31, Folder 8-10)
  - Association of American Universities, study of neighborhood problems of American urban universities, 1957-1958 (Box 31, Folder 11-12)
  - Association of American Universities, study of neighborhood problems of American universities, financing study, 1958-1960 (Box 32, Folder 1-2)
  - Association of American Universities, study of neighborhood problems of American universities, Ford Foundation proposal, 1958 (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Association of American University Presses, 1951-1959 (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Association of Community Councils, 1952-1955 (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Association of Governing Boards of State Universities, 1947-1959 (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Association of Graduate Schools, 1953-1960 (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - Association of Graduate Schools, annual meeting, Pasadena, 1955 (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - Association of Research Libraries, 1954-1960 (Box 32, Folder 9-10)
  - Association of Summer Session Deans and Directors, 1948-1953 (Box 32, Folder 11)
  - Association of Universities of the British Commonwealth, 1953-1959 (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Association of Universities of the British Commonwealth, visit to the University of Chicago campus, September 12-18, 1958 (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Association of University Evening Colleges, 1946-1960 (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Astronomy, Department of, 1953-1957 (Box 33, Folder 4-5)
  - Astronomy, Department of, McDonald Observatory, 1951-1956 (Box 33, Folder 6-7)
  - Astronomy, Department of, McDonald Observatory, budget and finance, 1951-1960 (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - Astronomy, Department of, Yerkes Observatory, 1928-1958 (Box 33, Folder 9-10)
  - Astronomy, Joint Department of, Chicago-Texas, 1957-1960 (Box 33, Folder 11)
  - Astronomy and Astrophysics, Department of, chairmanship, 1957 (Box 33, Folder 12)
  - Astronomy and Astrophysics, Department of, Yerkes Observatory, chairmanship, 1957 (Box 33, Folder 13)
  - Athletics, 1951-1960 (Box 33, Folder 14-16)
  - Atomic Energy Act, 1946-1952 (Box 33, Folder 17)
  - Atomic Energy Commission, 1945-1955 (Box 33, Folder 18-20)
  - Atomic Energy Commission, 1951-1958 (Box 34, Folder 1-3)
  - Atomic Energy Commission, press releases on subjects pertinent to university, 1960 (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Atomic Energy, First Self-Sustaining Chain Reaction, 10th Anniversary, 1952 (Box 34, Folder 5-6)
  - Atomic Energy, First Self-Sustaining Chain Reaction, 15th Anniversary, 1957 (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - Atomic Energy, International Conference on Peaceful Uses of, 1955-1960 (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - Atomic Energy, newspaper articles, etc., 1948-1955 (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Atomic Energy, postdoctoral and predoctoral fellowships, 1948- 1953 (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Atomic Energy, United States Congress Joint Committee on, 1950-1954 (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - Atomic Industrial Forum, Inc., 1954-1960 (Box 35, Folder 4-5)
  - Atomic Industrial Forum, Inc., the University of Chicago, membership, 1955-1960 (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - Auchincloss, Douglas, 1995 (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - Audio-Visual Center, 1945-1960 (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - Awards and prizes, Atoms for Peace award, 1955-1960 (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - Awards and prizes, American Chemical Society, 1958-1959 (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Awards and prizes, Washington award of the Western Society of Engineers, 1959 (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Baptist Graduate Student Center, university contributions and support, 1954-1960 (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Baptist Theological Union, annual dinners and citations, 1951-1960 (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - Baptist Theological Union, budget, finance, etc., Trustees Fund, 1945-1956 (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - Baptist Theological Union, Comptroller, 1946-1953 (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - Baptist Theological Union, Comptroller, 1953-1959 (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - Baptist Theological Union, Office of the Treasurer, 1953-1960 (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - Baptist Theological Union and Divinity School, Committee for Communication, 1954 (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - Barat College of the Sacred Heart, 1953 (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - Barber Shop, Reynolds Club, 1955 (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - Barnard, Harrison B., 1927-1952 (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - Bean, Donald P., 1959-1960 (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - Beaven, Joseph C., 1942-1952 (Box 37, Folder 8-9)
  - Behavioral Sciences, Ad Hoc Committee, October 1951-February 1952 (Box 37, Folder 10)
  - Behavioral Sciences at the University of Chicago, report, 1954-1955 (Box 37, Folder 11)
  - Behavioral Sciences at the University of Chicago, report, supplementary documents, 1954 (Box 37, Folder 12)
  - Behavioral Sciences, Committee on, new, 1949-March 1952 (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - Behavioral Sciences, Committee on, March 1952-March 1956 (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Behavioral Sciences, Dr. James G. Miller project, 1951-1955 (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - Behavioral Sciences, Report, Supplementary Documents, 1954 (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - Behavioral Sciences, self-study programs, background papers, February-July 1954 (Box 38, Folder 5-7)
  - Behavioral Sciences, self-study programs, background papers, August 1954-February 1955 (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Behavioral Sciences, self-study programs, Visiting Committee, 1953-1954 (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Bell, Laird, portrait, 1953-1954 (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Bemis, Edward W., 1930-1959 (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Benton, William, 1951-1959 (Box 39, Folder 5-7)
  - B, general, 1950-1955 (Box 39, Folder 8)
  - Big Ten Officers' Conference, 1954 (Box 39, Folder 9-10)
  - Big Ten Officers' Conference, 1955 (Box 40, Folder 1-4)
  - Big Ten Officers' Conference, mid-winter conference, November 19, 1956 (Box 40, Folder 5-6)
  - Biochemistry, Department of, 1951-1960 (Box 41, Folder 1-2)
  - Biological Sciences, Division of, 1950-1960 (Box 41, Folder 3-6)
  - Biological Sciences, Division of, Faculty Board, 1951-1954 (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - Biological Sciences, Division of, space, 1956-1959 (Box 41, Folder 8)
  - Biomedical Career Conference, 1960 (Box 41, Folder 9)
  - Biopsychology, Committee of, 1952-1953 (Box 41, Folder 10)
  - Blackfriars, 1957-1960 (Box 41, Folder 11)
  - Blake, Dan B. III, 1949-1954 (Box 41, Folder 12)
  - Blind Child Preschool Project, 1952-1955 (Box 41, Folder 13)
  - Block, Louis B., Fund for Basic Research and Advance Study, Annual Reports of the Board, 1956-1958 (Box 41, Folder 14)
  - Block, Louis, Fund, Board, 1956-1960 (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - Block, Louis, Fund, Board minutes and agenda, 1956-1960 (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - Block, Louis, Fund, Faculty Board, membership, 1955-1958 (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - Blue Cross and Blue Shield, 1951-1960 (Box 42, Folder 4-5)
  - Blue Cross and Blue Shield Plans, 1949-1951 (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - B’nai B'rith, 1953-1955 (Box 42, Folder 7)
  - Bookstore, 1951-1960 (Box 42, Folder 8-10)
  - Boston University, 1959-1960 (Box 42, Folder 11)
  - Botany, Department of, 1950-1960 (Box 42, Folder 12-13)
  - Botany, Department of, Bird Haven, 1950-1957 (Box 43, Folder 1-3)
  - Botany, Department of, H.M. Russell, daylilies matter, 1947-1954 (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - Bourbon-Busset, Jacques de, 1957 (Box 43, Folder 5)
  - Boy Scouts of America, 1952-1960 (Box 43, Folder 6-7)
  - Boyd's City Dispatch, Inc., 1942-1957 (Box 43, Folder 8)
  - Bradley University, 1949-1959 (Box 43, Folder 9)
  - Branch Banking in Chicago, Citizens’ Committee for, 1959 (Box 43, Folder 10)
  - Brandeis University, 1957-1959 (Box 43, Folder 11)
  - Britannica, Encyclopaedia, 1941-1960 (Box 43, Folder 12-16)
  - Britannica, Encyclopaedia, agreements and royalties, 1951-1960 (Box 44, Folder 1-6)
  - Britannica, Encyclopaedia, Board of Editors, 1949-1960 (Box 44, Folder 7)
  - Britannica, Encyclopaedia, Book of the Year, 1956-1960 (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Britannica, Encyclopaedia, financial statements, 1951-1955 (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - Britannica, Encyclopaedia, home study proposal, 1959-1960 (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - Britannica, Encyclopaedia, Junior Advisory Committee, membership, 1943-1957 (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - Britannica, Encyclopaedia, Junior Advisory Committee, minutes, 1943-1960 (Box 45, Folder 5-6)
  - Britannica, Encyclopaedia, minutes, 1950-1960 (Box 45, Folder 7-8)
  - Britannica, Encyclopaedia, minutes, 1950-1960 (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - Britannica, Encyclopaedia, 190th Anniversary and 15th Year of Affiliation with University of Chicago, 1958 (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - Britannica, Encyclopaedia, outside comments, 1942-1955 (Box 46, Folder 3-4)
  - Britannica, Encyclopaedia, Senior Advisory Committee, 1944-1954 (Box 46, Folder 5)
  - Britannica, Encyclopaedia, Senior Advisory Committee, 1956-1960 (Box 46, Folder 6)
  - Britannica, Encyclopaedia, Senior Advisory Committee, duties and fees, 1955 (Box 46, Folder 7)
  - Britannica, Encyclopaedia, Senior Advisory Committee, membership, 1952-1960 (Box 46, Folder 8)
  - Britannica, Encyclopaedia, Senior Advisory Committee, minutes, 1951-1958 (Box 46, Folder 9)
  - Britannica, Encyclopaedia, senior advisory committee, notices of meetings, 1955-1960 (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - Britannica, Encyclopaedia, space, 1951 (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - Britannica, Encyclopaedia, stockholders’ annual meeting, 1951-1960 (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - Britannica, Encyclopaedia, tax matters, 1953-1954 (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - Britannica Films, Inc., 1943-1960 (Box 47, Folder 5-7)
  - Britannica, Ltd., 1951 (Box 47, Folder 8)
  - British, 1958 (Box 47, Folder 9)
  - Brochures, general, 1940-1960 (Box 47, Folder 10-13)
  - Brookings Institution, Conference on Research on Graduate Education, February 27, 1959 (Box 47, Folder 14)
  - Brooklyn College, 1955-1960 (Box 47, Folder 15)
  - Brussels World's Fair, 1958 (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - Buck, Carl D., 1952 (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - Buffalo, University of, 1953-1960 (Box 48, Folder 3-4)
  - Building projects, general, 1951-1953 (Box 48, Folder 5)
  - Buildings, campus, Administration Building, allocation of space, 1956-1960 (Box 48, Folder 6)
  - Buildings, campus, Administration Building, budgets and finance, 1953 (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Buildings, campus, Administration Building, elevator problems, 1949-1958 (Box 48, Folder 8)
  - Buildings, campus, allocation of space, 1959 (Box 48, Folder 9)
  - Buildings, campus, Arts Center, proposed, 1951-1960 (Box 48, Folder 10)
  - Buildings, campus, Bell, Laird, law quadrangle, 1954-1960 (Box 48, Folder 11)
  - Buildings, campus, Bell, Laird, law quadrangle, memorials, 1956 (Box 48, Folder 12)
  - Buildings, campus, Blake, Gates, Cobb Hall, remodeling program, 1960 (Box 48, Folder 13)
  - Buildings, campus, budget, finance, projects, 1954-1959 (Box 48, Folder 14)
  - Buildings, campus, Classics, 1930-1958 (Box 48, Folder 15)
  - Buildings, campus, Cobb Hall, 1955 (Box 48, Folder 16)
  - Buildings, campus, Cobb Hall, renovation program, 1959-1960 (Box 48, Folder 17)
  - Buildings, campus, Culver Hall, 1951 (Box 48, Folder 18)
  - Buildings, campus, Eckhart, Bernard Albert, Hall, 1953-1958 (Box 48, Folder 19)
  - Buildings, campus, 1155 East 60th Street, site negotiations and agreements, 1952-1954 (Box 49, Folder 1)
  - Buildings, campus, 5720 Woodlawn, budget and finance, 1958-1960 (Box 49, Folder 2)
  - Buildings, campus, fire regulations, 1959-1960 (Box 49, Folder 3)
  - Buildings, campus, Jones Laboratory, 1953-1960 (Box 49, Folder 4)
  - Buildings, campus, Kent Chemical Laboratory, alterations, 1956-1960 (Box 49, Folder 5)
  - Buildings, campus, Law School, air conditioning, 1959-1960 (Box 49, Folder 6)
  - Buildings, campus, Lexington Hall, 1955-1957 (Box 49, Folder 7)
  - Buildings, campus, Library, University, budget, 1960 (Box 49, Folder 8)
  - Buildings, campus, Midway Studios, 1953-1957 (Box 49, Folder 9)
  - Buildings, campus, Mott, Charles Stewart, Building, cornerstone ceremony, 1958 (Box 49, Folder 10)
  - Buildings, campus, Mott, Charles Stewart, Building, dedication ceremonies, 1959 (Box 49, Folder 11)
  - Buildings, campus, 970 East 58th Street, 1953 (Box 49, Folder 12)
  - Buildings, campus, Press building, 1956 (Box 49, Folder 13)
  - Buildings, campus, renewal and replacement, budget and finance, 1952-1960 (Box 49, Folder 14)
  - Buildings, campus, Reynolds Club, 1951-1956 (Box 49, Folder 15)
  - Buildings, campus, Rosenwald Hall, 1956-1958 (Box 49, Folder 16)
  - Buildings, campus, Ryerson Physical Laboratory, 1955-1960 (Box 49, Folder 17)
  - Buildings, campus, School of Social Service Administration, 1958-1959 (Box 49, Folder 18)
  - Buildings, campus, Social Science Research Building, 1954 (Box 49, Folder 19)
  - Buildings, campus, south campus redevelopment project, 1958-1960 (Box 49, Folder 20)
  - Buildings, campus, Swift Hall, 1956-1959 (Box 49, Folder 21)
  - Buildings, campus, Taft House, 1954 (Box 49, Folder 22)
  - Buildings, campus, University High School, budget and finance, 1956-1960 (Box 50, Folder 1)
  - Buildings, campus, University High School, budget and finance, 1957-1960 (Box 50, Folder 2)
  - Buildings, campus, Walker Museum, 1892-1959 (Box 50, Folder 3)
  - Buildings, campus, Yerkes Observatory, property holdings, Williams Bay, 1960 (Box 50, Folder 4)
  - Buildings, campus, Yerkes Observatory, George Williams College negotiations, 1950-1960 (Box 50, Folder 5)
  - Buildings, dormitories and residence halls, 1953-1957 (Box 50, Folder 6)
  - Buildings, dormitories and residence halls, Blackstone Hall, 1956-1959 (Box 51, Folder 1)
  - Buildings, dormitories and residence halls, budget and finance, 1954-1960 (Box 51, Folder 2-3)
  - Buildings, dormitories and residence halls, Burton-Judson Hall, possible use by Law School, 1960 (Box 51, Folder 4)
  - Buildings, dormitories and residence halls, nurses’ residences, Blackstone Hall, 1954-1955 (Box 51, Folder 5)
  - Buildings, dormitories and residence halls, nurses’ residences, proposed, 1956-1960 (Box 51, Folder 6)
  - Buildings, dormitories and residence halls, nurses’ residences, 6104 Woodlawn Avenue, 1953-1956 (Box 51, Folder 7)
  - Buildings, dormitories and residence halls, nurses’ residences, 6022 Drexel Avenue, 1952 (Box 51, Folder 8)
  - Buildings, dormitories and residence halls, occupancy, 1955-1960 (Box 51, Folder 9)
  - Buildings, dormitories and residence halls, Pierce Hall, 1957-1960 (Box 51, Folder 10)
  - Buildings, dormitories and residence halls, Pierce Hall, budget and finance, 1957-1959 (Box 51, Folder 11)
  - Buildings, dormitories and residence halls, Pierce Hall, budget and finance, 1960 (Box 51, Folder 12)
  - Buildings, dormitories and residence halls, Snell-Hitchcock Hall, 1957 (Box 51, Folder 13)
  - Buildings, dormitories and residence halls, Woodward Court, 1955-1960 (Box 52, Folder 1)
  - Buildings, hospitals and clinics, alterations, renovations, 1951-1959 (Box 52, Folder 2)
  - Buildings, medical center, Armour, Philip, Clinical Research Building, 1958-1960 (Box 52, Folder 3)
  - Buildings, medical center, Bobs Roberts Hospital for Children, 1956-1960 (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - Buildings, medical center, Carlson, Anton Julius, Animal Research Facility, 1960 (Box 52, Folder 5)
  - Buildings, medical center, Cummings Life Science Center, 1957-1958 (Box 52, Folder 6)
  - Buildings, medical center, Goldblatt Magnetic Resonance Imaging Center, 1960 (Box 52, Folder 7)
  - Buildings, medical center, Goldblatt Pavilion, 1955-1960 (Box 52, Folder 8)
  - Buildings, medical center, Mothers Aid Pavilion, 1956-1960 (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Buildings, medical center, Ricketts, 1956 (Box 53, Folder 2)
  - Buildings, medical center, Smith, Charles Gilman, Hospital, 1951-1960 (Box 53, Folder 3)
  - Buildings, medical center, Smith, Charles Gilman, Hospital, budget and finance, 1951-1957 (Box 53, Folder 4)
  - Buildings, medical center, Smith, Charles Gilman, Hospital, budget and finance, John Hancock loan, 1951-1954 (Box 53, Folder 5)
  - Buildings, medical center, Smith, Charles Gilman, Hospital, financing of, 1952-1955 (Box 53, Folder 6)
  - Buildings, medical center, University of Chicago clinics, 1955-1956 (Box 53, Folder 7)
  - Buildings and Grounds, Department of, 1951-1955 (Box 53, Folder 8)
  - Buildings and Grounds, Department of, fire regulations affecting educational institutions, 1959 (Box 53, Folder 9)
  - Buildings and Grounds, Department of, Geophysical Sciences, "Proposed Building for Geophysical Sciences," prepared by Pace Associates, 1960 (Box 53, Folder 10)
  - Buildings and Grounds, Department of, Laird Bell Law Quadrangle, dedication, October 5, 1959, and dedicatory year activities, 1959- 1960 (Box 53, Folder 11)
  - Buildings and Grounds, Department of, Laird Bell Law Quadrangle, dedication, October 5, 1959, and dedicatory year activities, 1959-1960 (Box 54, Folder 1-2)
  - Buildings and Grounds, Department of, Laird Bell Law Quadrangle, Weymouth Kirkland Courtroom, 1957 (Box 54, Folder 3)
  - Buildings and Grounds, Department of, Medical Center, "Feasibility Report for Proposed Air Conditioning of Medical Buildings and Hospitals," 1958 (Box 54, Folder 4)
  - Buildings and Grounds, Department of, Medical Center, "Feasibility Report for Proposed Air Conditioning of Medical Buildings and Hospitals," Supplements, 1960 (Box 54, Folder 5)
  - Buildings and Grounds, Department of, Medical Center, Goldblatt Pavilion, Groundbreaking, April 15, 1959 (Box 54, Folder 6)
  - Buildings and Grounds, Department of, Medical Center, Hospital Hotel, proposed, 1947-1955 (Box 54, Folder 7-8)
  - Buildings and Grounds, Department of, President's House, 5640 Woodlawn Avenue, 1945-1952 (Box 55, Folder 1)
  - Buildings and Grounds, Department of, University High School, 1955-1960 (Box 55, Folder 2-4)
  - Buildings and Grounds, Department of, Yerkes Observatory, dome, 1958 (Box 55, Folder 5)
  - Bulletin of the Atomic Scientists, 1946-1960 (Box 55, Folder 6-7)
  - Bulletin of the Atomic Scientists, space, 1952-1960 (Box 55, Folder 8)
  - Burma, 1953-1954 (Box 55, Folder 9)
  - Bursar's Office, 1950-1960 (Box 55, Folder 10-11)
  - Business, Graduate School of, 1960 (Box 55, Folder 12)
  - Business, Graduate School of, Committee Associates’ Program, 1957-1960 (Box 55, Folder 13)
  - Business, Graduate School of, executive program, 1950-1957 (Box 56, Folder 1-2)
  - Business, Graduate School of, executive program club, 1955-1957 (Box 56, Folder 3)
  - Business, Graduate School of, management conferences, 1960 (Box 56, Folder 4)
  - Business, Graduate School of, non-academic personnel and purchasing, 1957-1960 (Box 56, Folder 5)
  - Business, Graduate School of, use of funds and method of accounting, 1955-1959 (Box 56, Folder 6)
  - Business Manager, Campus Operations, 1951-1954 (Box 56, Folder 7-8)
  - Business Manager and Campus Operations, Office of, 1952-1960 (Box 56, Folder 9)
  - Business Manager, Campus Operations, Commons and residence halls, 1951-1960 (Box 56, Folder 10-11)
  - Business Manager, Campus Operations, Power Plant, L.R. Flook's material, 1934-1959 (Box 56, Folder 12)
  - Business Manager, Campus Operations, Power Plant, steam and electricity, 1940-1954 (Box 56, Folder 13)
  - Business Problems Bureau, 1952 (Box 57, Folder 1)
  - Business, School of, 1944-1959 (Box 57, Folder 2-9)